[{
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "partner means:",
    "answers": ["thanks", "penny", "kettle", "associate"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "freedom means:",
    "answers": ["pupil", "liberty", "mama", "cushion"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "terrible means:",
    "answers": ["dreadful", "plump", "certain", "elderly"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "dirty means:",
    "answers": ["happy", "grateful", "filthy", "costly"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "postage means:",
    "answers": ["young child", "stamps", "autumn", "garbage"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "pony means:",
    "answers": ["alarm", "dried grape", "movie", "small horse"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "glitter means:",
    "answers": ["retain", "hearten", "sparkle", "clout"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "toddler means:",
    "answers": ["young child", "heap", "work", "favor"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "buddy means:",
    "answers": ["daybreak", "enrollment", "pal", "madman"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "English Vocabulary",
    "question": "octagon means:",
    "answers": ["clunk", "skepticism", "fragments", "eight-sided figure"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "What % of scientists agree that climate change is likely generated by human activities?",
    "answers": ["84%", "50%", "97%", "11%"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Global warming is an observed century-scale rise in the ___ of the Earth's climate",
    "answers": [
      "Maximum temperature",
      "Temperature",
      "Minimum temperature",
      "Average temperature"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "How can extreme events like hurricanes, drought, & wildfires impact energy infrastructure?",
    "answers": [
      "Water shortages",
      "Power outages",
      "Higher electricity & gas prices",
      "All of these things"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Food waste contributes to how many carbon emissions?",
    "answers": [
      "500 million metric tons",
      "3 billion metric tons",
      "200 million metric tons",
      "7 billion metric tons"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "____ is when land becomes a desert, typically losing its bodies of water, vegetation and wildlife.",
    "answers": ["Heatwave", "Desertification", "Hurricane", "Drought"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Which of the following is a greenhouse gas?",
    "answers": ["CH4", "CO2", "Water Vapor", "All of them"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Which lake has dried up by 90% due to rising temperatures?",
    "answers": ["Lake Chad", "Lake Michigan", "Lake Malawi", "Lake Como"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Which of these countries emits the most carbon dioxide?",
    "answers": ["USA", "Russia", "China", "UK"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "Why are forests important for mitigating climate change?",
    "answers": [
      "Leaves of trees reflect all sunlight away from the Earth",
      "Trees are an important food source",
      "They play an integral part in the carbon cycle",
      "Trees provide building materials"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "Climate Action",
    "question": "How long does it take for carbon dioxide in the atmosphere to disperse?",
    "answers": ["1 year", "50 years", "100 years", "500 years"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which food is a staple of India?",
    "answers": ["okra", "barley", "rye", "rice"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "What are the benefits of 'composting?'",
    "answers": [
      "It can reduce climate impact.",
      "It reduces the soil's need for chemical fertilizers.",
      "All of these statements are true.",
      "It can recycle nutrients."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
    "answers": [
      "The majority of food donated by WFP is grown in the USA.",
      "The developed nations are best able to find solutions to hunger.",
      "Most of the hungry people in the world live in Africa.",
      "Hunger is the world's greatest solvable problem."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "What is the term for farmland created by cutting down and burning forests?",
    "answers": [
      "transhumance",
      "slash-and-burn agriculture",
      "shifting cultivation",
      "no-till agriculture"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Hunger kills more than _____ combined",
    "answers": [
      "Tetanus, diarrhoea and Scurvy",
      "Cirrhosis, Gout and Cancer",
      "Malaria, Whooping Cough and Diabetes",
      "HIV/AIDS, Malaria and Tuberculosis"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true?",
    "answers": [
      "Famine is an unavoidable disaster.",
      "Famine is preventable.",
      "Famine is caused exclusively by drought.",
      "Famine is caused by natural seasonal cycles."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which of the following options is not a main cause of hunger?",
    "answers": [
      "increase in food prices",
      "war and conflict",
      "natural disasters and climate change",
      "the declining number of farmers"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "What are meat, eggs, diary products, seeds, nuts and legumes good sources of?",
    "answers": ["fat", "protein", "carbohydrates", "sugar"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which food is a staple of China?",
    "answers": ["rice", "fava bean", "apples", "yams"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Healthy Eating",
    "question": "Which of the following options is not a specialized nutritional product?",
    "answers": [
      "high-energy biscuits",
      "raspberry puree",
      "compressed food bars",
      "fortified blended foods"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "Where should you follow health advice from?",
    "answers": [
      "Rumours that you see on social networking sites or sent to you via chat",
      "Your local health authority and the World Health Organization"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "Should you wash your hands after coughing or sneezing?",
    "answers": [
      "Always. Frequent handwashing is one of the most effective ways to avoid infection.",
      "No, it doesn't matter."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "What does 'self-isolation' mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Staying at home and not leaving for 14 days to avoid spreading contagion to others",
      "When you feel mentally isolated",
      "When you're in a place without that many people"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "If I hear a crazy rumour about the coronavirus, should I let others know?",
    "answers": [
      "No. Spreading rumours can create panic, anxiety, or misinformation. Always check sources.",
      "Yes. It's important to tell everyone what I've heard, even if I don't know the source."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "If you have a family member or friend in self-isolation, it's important to:",
    "answers": [
      "Check in with them regularly via phone or email to make sure they're ok",
      "Ignore them",
      "Frequently visit them in person",
      "Stigmatize them in case they are sick"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "Don't touch your ______ to better protect yourself from the new coronavirus.",
    "answers": [
      "Pockets",
      "Eyes, nose, and mouth",
      "Ears and shoulders",
      "Feet"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "If you use a tissue when you cough or sneeze, what should you do with it after?",
    "answers": [
      "You can re-use it, it's fine.",
      "Throw it away immediately. Never re-use soiled tissues. Wash hands as soon as you can."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "What is the minimum distance you should maintain during 'social distancing'?",
    "answers": [
      "At least one meter (three feet)",
      "It doesn't matter",
      "Half a meter"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "Spitting in public is fine, even during a COVID-19 outbreak.",
    "answers": [
      "Yes. There is no risk if people spit in public.",
      "No. Saliva is one of the ways contagion is spread, and spitting should be avoided."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "category": "Coronavirus",
    "question": "What are the most common symptoms of COVID-19?",
    "answers": [
      "Numbness in toes",
      "Ringing in ears",
      "Fever, cough, and difficulty breathing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }
]